### Hezekiah Morgan Chukwudi

Address: Irete, Owerri, Nigeria Nationality: Nigeria

Date of birth: 1999-09-23

Mobile Contact: +234 81 225 10 760

Email address: morganhezekiah1@gmail.com

### **Profile**

I have a deep understanding of many technical subjects. I am an avid open source developer. I love to be creative and inventive. I have over 5 years of experience in the field. More documentation of experience, references and skills are available upon request.

#### **CAREER TARGET**

To develop software applications to enhance human existence, defend my employers excellence and help me improve.

### Work experience

3/2020- present, Software Engineer, IcodeTech LLC, Ihiagwa, Nigeria

 Maintaining and updating web and mobile applications. This mainly involved developing web api's with django restframework and consuming the endpoints through android or react js frontends.

Technologies used: Python, JavaScript, HTML5, Jsx, APIs, Java, Android studio

7/2018 – 01/2020, Web Developer,

• Creating web applications and contents for educational institutions.

Technologies used: Python, JavaScript, HTML5, Jsx, APIs,

# Education

09/2017 - present, Mechatronics Engineering Federal University Of Technology ,Owerri Imo state Nigeria.

Earning a Bachelor of Engineering in Mechatronics and a minor in Software development.

# **Skills**

# Languages

Java Python JavaScript

## **Version Control**

Git Bitbucket

### Web

- HTML5
- XML
- Stylesheets( css, sass and scss, Bootstrap, material ui)

#### **Databases**

- Oracle
- MySQL
- Sqlite
- PostGres db

## **Frameworks**

- Django
- React js
- Android studio
- Django restframework

#### **HOBBIES**

Chess, Soccer, Music